Guide to Tuli Kupferberg and Sylvia Topp Papers MSS.385
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI. Research and Source Material, 1821-2010; 1960-1995; 70 Linear Feet in 50 record cartons, 23 manuscript boxes, 1 flat folder, 2 flat boxes, 5 oversize flat boxes
  - Subseries A. Research and Subject files, 1821-2010; 1960-1995; 52 Linear Feet in 50 record cartons, 1 flat box, 1 flat folder, 2 oversize flat boxes
    - Prophecy and Apocalypse, 1973-1983 (Box 84, Folder 17-18)
    - Protect and Survive, 1978-1988 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - Protest and Boycott Research, 1969-1970 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Protest and Demonstration, 1967-1976 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Protest and War, 1968-1969 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Protests, Advertisements, 1968-1969 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Protests, Anti-War Demonstrations, RAT, LA Free Press, 1968-1969 (Box 84, Folder 24-25)
    - Protests, Draft, 1965-1968 (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - Proverbs and Small Pieces, 1977-1983 (Box 84, Folder 27)
    - Public Nuisance, undated (Box 84, Folder 28)
    - Publications -- Counterpunch; Teen Digest; Paranoia, 1959-2001 (Box 84, Folder 29)
    - Punk Zines -- John Crawford Correspondence -- "Damaged Goods"; "Inside Joke"; "Slam Rag", 1981-1982 (Box 84, Folder 30)
    - Quotes: Bibliography, 1978-1979, undated (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Radpol, 1995-2001 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Radiation and Atomic Research, 1964-1968 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Radical and Leftist Publication Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 85, Folder 4-5)
    - Radical and Left-Wing Literature, 1982-1985 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Radical Humor, 1959-1986 (Box 85, Folder 7-18)
    - Radical Humor Canada, 1945, International Treasury of Left Wing Humor / Contemporary Publications Winnipeg, circa 1945 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Radical Humor -- Presidents, 1979-1981 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Radical Humor -- Shoplifting, 1973-1979 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Radical Press -- RAT, LA Free Press, Anonymous Actions Anonymous, 1967-1969 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Radical Traditionalist Papers -- Whitney Catalogs, 1973-1987 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Radicalism and Communism, 1978, undated (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Radio Werewolf, undated (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - Reaganation, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - Recreative Review, 1821 -- Lee Scharf, 1821, 1997 (Box 85, Folder 27)
    - Recruiting, 1963-1977 (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - The Red Prussian -- Leopold Schwarzschild, 1947 (Box 85, Folder 29)
    - Refuse and Resist, 1987-1988 (Box 85, Folder 30)
    - Rejects, undated (Box 85, Folder 31)
    - Rejected Labor, undated (Box 85, Folder 32)
    - Religion, 1957-1995, undated (Box 196, Folder 21)
    - Religion, 1958-2001 (Box 86, Folder 1-7)
    - Religion, Cults, 1961, 1983-1986 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Religion, God, Cults, 1972-1986 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Remarks / Correspondence on Unidentified Novel, 1996 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Reporters with No Message, undated (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Republican Like Me -- Sparrow -- Soft Skull Press, 1997 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Research Correspondence -- "To Send For", 1968-1969 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Research Topics, 1980-1982 (Box 86, Folder 14-15)
    - Resist Concert, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Review, 1965, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - "Revolting Art" Research and Notes, 1987-1989 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Revolting Ideas Notes, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Revolutionary, 1964, 1983-1987 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Revolutionary Advertisements, 1968-1970 (Box 86, Folder 21-22)
    - Revolutionary and Industrial Images, undated (Box 86, Folder 23)
    - RH, 1983-1990 (Box 86, Folder 24-25)
    - Ribicoff -- Daley, 1996 (Box 86, Folder 26)
    - Right Makes Might, 2007 (Box 86, Folder 27)
    - Robb Report Magazine, 1995-1996 (Box 86, Folder 28)
    - Robert Maxwell, 1992-1994 (Box 86, Folder 29)
    - Rockefeller, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 30)
    - Rosa and Karl, undated (Box 86, Folder 31)
    - Royalty, 1969-2001 (Box 86, Folder 32-33)
    - Rushdie, 1988-1989 (Box 86, Folder 34)
    - Russia and Communism in Popular Culture, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 35)
    - Russia, Bosnia, 1994-1998 (Box 86, Folder 36)
    - Russian History Textbook, undated (Box 86, Folder 37)
    - Russian Mafia, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 38)
    - S and M, 1966, undated (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Sadistics, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Safe Methods of Business, undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Safety: General, 1972-1980 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Salute to Journalism, 1992-1995 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Santa Suicide, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Saudi, undated (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Scholastic Scope Magazine / Organize Contest, 1995 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Science, 1960, 1972-1983 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Scientists, 1968-1969 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Scientology, 1969 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Screaming Catholics, 1995 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Scufflin, 1962-1979 (Box 87, Folder 12-14)
    - Second, 1967 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Selenium, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Self-Image, 1988-1989 (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Sex, 1880, 1916, 1946-2000 (Box 87, Folder 18-32)
    - Sex, 1960s, Health and Body, 1964-1968 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Sex, Alfred J. Heinecke Letter, 1965-1968 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Sex and Body, 1962-1970 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Sex and Politicians, Peace Eye, 1964-1976 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Sex Come Ons, 1983-1991 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Sex (Early File), 1911, 1917, 1965-1983 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - The Sex Education Racket -- Book, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Sex, Human Body, 1967, undated (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Sex -- Illustrations, 1960-1968, undated (Box 88, Folder 9-10)
    - Sex in the 1960s, 1935-1969 (Box 88, Folder 11-14)
    - Sex -- La Plume, 1967-1968, undated (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Sex -- Maybe, undated (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Sex -- Miscellaneous, 1965-1968 (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Sex -- New, 1969, undated (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Sex -- NS, 1969-1971 (Box 88, Folder 19-22)
    - Sex -- Old, undated (Box 88, Folder 23)
    - Sex Stink, 1960, undated (Box 88, Folder 24)
    - Sex -- Yes, 1949, 1964-1968 (Box 88, Folder 25)
    - Sexed, 1962-1975 (Box 88, Folder 26)
    - Sexist Pig, undated (Box 88, Folder 27)
    - Sexuality and Pornography, 1969-1970 (Box 88, Folder 28)
    - Sexuality -- Letter from Helen -- Notes for The Intersexual Chicago DNC, 1969-1970 (Box 88, Folder 29)
    - Shadow Press, Homelessness, Iraq War, Police, 1982-2007 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Shimon Tzabar, "Some Crime, Some Punishment", undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Shitrology, 1985-1991 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Shoah Business, 2000-2001 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Sing for Your Fucking, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Sixties Advertisements, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Sixties Protest Material -- Up Against the Wall, Motherfucker, 1963-1969 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Small Children's Books, 1960-1997 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Smoking, 1987-2008 (Box 89, Folder 9-14)
    - Smoking -- Advertisements -- Cigarettes, 1989-2002 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Smoking -- Advertisements -- Quitting, 1990-2003 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Smoking -- Anti-Smoking Activism, 1991-2003 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Smoking -- Articles, 1988-2002 (Box 89, Folder 18-19)
    - Smoking -- Cartoons, 1991-2001 (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Smoking -- CDC Second-Hand Smoke Folder, undated (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Smoking -- Health Information, 1991-1995 (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - Smoking -- Helmsboro Country, 1988-1990 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Smoking -- MMWR (CDC) -- Vol. 36, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - Smoking -- MMWR (CDC) -- Vol. 39, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - Smoking -- MMWR (CDC) -- Vol. 40, 1991 (Box 89, Folder 26)
    - Smoking -- MMWR (CDC) -- Vol. 41, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 27)
    - Smoking -- MMWR (CDC) -- Vol. 42, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 28)
    - Smoking -- MMWR (CDC) -- Vol. 43, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 29)
    - Smoking -- MMWR (CDC) -- Vol. 51, 52, 54, 2002-2005 (Box 89, Folder 30)
    - Smoking -- Notes and Fragments, 2008 (Box 89, Folder 31)
    - Smoking -- Philip Morris Magazine, 1988-1991 (Box 89, Folder 32-34)
    - Smoking -- Philip Morris Safety Assessment, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Smoking -- Promotions, 1993-1995 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Smoking -- Smoke Free Air -- Newsletter, 1992-1995 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Smoking -- Tobacco-Free Youth Reporter, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - "Sniperscope" Illustration, 1996-1999 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Snowball Fights, 1960-1981 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Social Castes, 1991-2003 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Sociology, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Soldier of Fortune Magazine -- Cover Copy, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Song Lyrics, 2002-2003 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Songs of the Nation, undated (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Space Illustrations, 1961-1974 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Spiegelman and Cartooning, 1999-2000 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Spike Jones and His City Slickers, 1990-2002 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Spirituality and Purity, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Sports, 1963-1987 (Box 90, Folder 16-17)
    - Sports and Dying, 1966-1978 (Box 90, Folder 18-19)
    - Sports (Fatalities), 1965-1974 (Box 90, Folder 20-21)
    - Sports Illustrations, 1973-1983 (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Sports Injuries, 1954-1983 (Box 90, Folder 23-24)
    - Squat Evictions in East Village, 1989-1990 (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - Squatting, Health -- Notes, 1993-2002 (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - Stairway to Grave, 1977-1991 (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - Stalinism and Art, 1988-1989 (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - The Standard, 1999-2000 (Box 90, Folder 29)
    - Stars and Bars, 2007 (Box 90, Folder 30)
    - Stern Sue, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 31)
    - Steven Brill, Content Magazine, 1997-1998 (Box 90, Folder 32)
    - Stewart Sanders, The Communards, undated (Box 90, Folder 33)
    - Stop the Music, undated (Box 90, Folder 34)
    - Student Protests, Draft, War, 1968-1969 (Box 90, Folder 35)
    - Student Rallies, Speeches, and Protests, 1966-1976 (Box 90, Folder 36)
    - Style, 1962-1982 (Box 90, Folder 37)
    - Suicide, 1967-1973 (Box 90, Folder 38-39)
    - Swastika / Hitler, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 40)
    - Sweet Potato Man -- LES 1923, undated (Box 90, Folder 41)
    - Sweethearts on Parade Score, undated (Box 90, Folder 42)
    - Taki, 2000 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Tales of Cap and Com, undated (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Teach Yourself Fucking / Fallen Political Figures, 1987-1992 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Teachers, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Technology and Advertising, 1958-1963 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Television and Media, War, 1961-2000 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Television, Media, War Clippings, 1983-2001 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Ten Talks to Girls on Health Book, 1921 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Terrorism, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Thank God for My Tapeworm, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Theodore A. Hall, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Therapy, Esalen, 1967-1968 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Theresienstadt, 1996-1999 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Thomas Forcade, 1978-1979 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Tian Dayton on Laughter, 2009 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - "'Til the Doctor Goes", 1977 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Tim Goldstein, "The News at Any Cost", circa 1986 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Timothy Leary Obituary, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Timothy Leary -- Start Your Own Religion (Photocopy), 1967 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Tis the Reason, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - To Frame, 1993-1995 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - To Work, 1978-1979 (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - Toast Mona Lisa, undated (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - Tobacco, 1971-2002 (Box 91, Folder 24-25)
    - Tobacco and Smoking, 1999-2007 (Box 91, Folder 26)
    - Tobacco / [ Listen to the Mockingbird Songs], 1980, undated (Box 91, Folder 27)
    - Tobacco Sham, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 28)
    - Todentanzers, 1962-1974 (Box 91, Folder 29)
    - Tom Wolfe, The Pump House Gang, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 30)
    - Tompkins Square -- 1874, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 31)
    - Too Old, 1995 (Box 91, Folder 32)
    - Toronto Clippings and Mailings, 1971, undated (Box 91, Folder 33)
    - Travel, undated (Box 91, Folder 34)
    - Trazodone Information, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 35)
    - Trotsky: Perm Rev, undated (Box 91, Folder 36)
    - Tuli, Thelma Blitz, Jeffrey Lewis, 2005-2006 (Box 91, Folder 37)
    - TV, 1978, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 38)
    - Ugly Mania, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 39)
    - Unbearable Lifetime Non-Achievement Award, undated (Box 91, Folder 40)
    - Uncle Sam, 1967, undated (Box 91, Folder 41)
    - Underground Surrealist -- Beats -- Liberation News, 1972-1994 (Box 91, Folder 42)
    - Unhappy the Land that Needs Heroes, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 43)
    - Unidentified 1970s Files, 1970-1980 (Box 91, Folder 44-45)
    - The Unknown Karl Marx, 1981, undated (Box 91, Folder 46)
    - Urology, 1949-1966 (Box 91, Folder 47)
    - U.S. History, Industrialization, Levines, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 48)
    - US -- NY, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 49)
    - U.S. Redivivus, 2002, undated (Box 91, Folder 50)
    - U.S. Research, 1989-2008 (Box 91, Folder 51-52, Box 92, Folder 1-2)
    - Uzi Does It, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Vaginas, undated (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Vanunu, 1993-1994 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Vegan Action No. 1 and No. 2, undated (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Venice via Book, undated (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Victor Herbert and Medical Files, 1997-1998 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Victoria's Secret, undated (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Vienne -- Time Life -- David Pryce -- Jones, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Vietnam, 1970-1971 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Vietnam and Protest Movement, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Vietnam, Civil Rights -- Clippings, 1963-1973 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Vietnam Images, Sex, Draft Protest, 1965-1970 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Vietnam Protest Flyers and Handbills, 1968-1969 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Vietnam, Protests, 1968-1971 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Vietnam, Protests, Draft, 1969-1970 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Vietnam, Sex, Protest Movement, 1964-1969 (Box 92, Folder 18-19)
    - Vietnam War, 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Vietnam, War, Protest -- Clippings, 1966-1968 (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - The Village Idiot, 1964-1968 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - Village Music, 1979 (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - Village Voice Comic, 1977-1996 (Box 92, Folder 24)
    - Violence, 1959-1968 (Box 92, Folder 25-28)
    - Violence and Media, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder 29)
    - Violence / Extra Songs, 1966-1969 (Box 92, Folder 30)
    - Von Links, undated (Box 92, Folder 31)
    - Vonnegut, Felix Dennis, Iraq, 2001-2007 (Box 92, Folder 32)
    - Wagner, 1997 (Box 92, Folder 33)
    - Want Ad Extras, 1968, undated (Box 92, Folder 34)
    - Want Ads, 1962-1968 (Box 92, Folder 35-36)
    - War, 1945, 1960-2001 (Box 93, Folder 1-7)
    - War and Combat, 1962-2003 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - War and Combat -- The Hunter Magazine, 1968-2003 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - War and Protest, 2002-2003 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - War, Draft, 1960s, Drugs, 1967-1968 (Box 93, Folder 11-12)
    - War Illustrations, 1993-2004 (Box 93, Folder 13-15)
    - War Image, 1977-1987 (Box 93, Folder 16-17)
    - The War is Over, undated (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - War, Politics, Sex, 1958-1969 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - War / Radiation, 1953-1959 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - War Resister's League -- Protests, Sit-Ins, Flyers, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - Warhol, 1968-1978 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - "Warhola" -- Murder Can Be Fun, Warhol Retrospectives, 1987-1989 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Was Karl Marx a Satanist? -- Richard Wurmbrand, 1976, undated (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Welfare Chains, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Westway, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Whacha Gonna Draw Now?, undated (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Whales, 1969-1974 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - What Away, 1974-1978 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Which Lies Behind?, 2001 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - White Collar Zoo -- Book, 1949 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Who's Who in America and Fuck Dictionary, 2003 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Willow Island, 1978 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Wisdom, 1976 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Woman, 1974, undated (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Women Against Pornography, 1980-1982 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Woodlawn, undated (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Words without Songs, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Work, 1927-1970 (Box 94, Folder 18-22)
    - Work and Capitalism Research, 1971-1978 (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - Work and Labor Research, 1971-1982 (Box 94, Folder 24-25)
    - Work / Notes, 1968-1969 (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - Work Secondaries, 1932-1967 (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - Work: The Job Itself, 1976-1978 (Box 94, Folder 28)
    - Workers, 1970-1972 (Box 94, Folder 29)
    - Workers and Left, undated (Box 94, Folder 30)
    - Working, 1967-1969 (Box 94, Folder 31)
    - Workplace Violence, 1959-1989 (Box 94, Folder 32-33)
    - World's Worst Sex, 1963-1982 (Box 94, Folder 34)
    - Worst Books List, 1969-1973 (Box 94, Folder 35)
    - Writers and Publishing, 1941-1980 (Box 94, Folder 36-37)
    - Writers Lives, 1930s, 1960-1963, undated (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Writing, 1960-1963 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Writing Articles and Advertisements, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Writing as a Disease, 1995 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Writing in America, 1940, 1972-1981 (Box 95, Folder 5-6)
    - Writing Life, 1962-1985 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Writing Proverbs, 1962-1978 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Writing Research, 1958-1985 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Writing Technique Quotations, undated (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Wuppertal, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - WWII Museum, 2007 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Xerox, 1987-1990 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Xian Communism, undated (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - X-mas, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - X-mas / New Years, 1962, undated (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - X-mas -- Old, 1972-1975 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Yellow Book Illustrated, 1939 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Yellow Pages, 1997, undated (Box 95, Folder 19-20)
    - Yeltsin Obituary -- The Nation, 2007 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Yes (Journal), undated (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - Young Hegelianism, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - The Young Hegelians -- McLellan, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - The Young Hegelians -- William J. Brazill, 1970 (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - Youth and Art, undated (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - Youth Violence Prevention, 2001 (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - Zappa Fan Page Interview, 2007 (Box 95, Folder 28)
    - General, 1859-2009 (Box 95, Folder 29-34, Box 96, Folder 1-17, Box 97, Folder 1-16, Box 98, Box 99, Folder 1-18, Box 100, Box 101, Folder 1-12, Box 209, Folder 1-13, Box 146, Folder 6, Box 264, Folder 13, Box 327, Folder 2)
    - General Posters, Illustrations, Event Announcements, 1842, 1875, 1918, 1920-1930, 1960-2009 (Box 103, Folder 1-9, Box 102, Folder 1-6, Box 40, Box 326, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Subseries B. Source Publications, 1863, 1869, 1899-1900, 1923, 1933-2009, undated; 12 Linear Feet in 22 manuscript boxes, 1 flat box, 3 oversize boxes
    This series is listed alphabetically.
    This series includes publications used by Kuperferberg and Topp for source material for writings, collages, music, and cartoons. These publications include local New York zines, underground newspapers, small press literary magazines, and international journals. Some publication topics include anarchy, politics, protests, sex, art, and humor. Publication dates range from the mid-1800s to 2009. The majority were published in the 1970s-1990s.
    Duplicate copies as well as issues of publications already held within Bobst Library and the Special Collections Libraries were deaccessioned.
    - @-Wire, 1992 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - 3 Acre Floor, 1996 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - 1000 New Jokes, 1935 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - 1917: Journal of the International Bolshevik Tendency, 1987-1996 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - A Draft Proposal for an Anarchist Black Cross Group, circa 1979 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Abolishing the Borders from Below, 2003 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - About Face, 1982 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - The Activist, 1991 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Aesthetic Realism Foundation, 1993, 1996 (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - After the Fall, undated (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - The Agent, 1980-1987 (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Agit-Pop America, 1996 (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - A.I.C. Open Channel, 1992 (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Ain't it Time We Got Mad!, 1992 (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - Alligator Unite Socialist of America American Liberation League, circa 1966 (Box 211, Folder 13)
    - Alpha Null, 1983 (Box 211, Folder 14)
    - Alternative Media, 1980-1983 (Box 211, Folder 15)
    - Alternative Press Review, 1994-2001 (Box 211, Folder 16)
    - AM Here Books, 1991-1992 (Box 211, Folder 17)
    - American Handgunner, 1986 (Box 211, Folder 18)
    - Amex / Canada, 1973 (Box 211, Folder 19)
    - An Outline of Guild Socialism, undated (Box 211, Folder 20)
    - Anarchist Age Weekly Review, 2001 (Box 211, Folder 21)
    - Anarchist Review, 1977-1980 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Anarchist Song Book, 1986 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Anarchist Yellow Pages, 1999 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Anarcho-Syndicalist Review, 2002-2004 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Anarchy, circa 1979 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Anarchy: A Journal of Desire Armed, 1988-2008 (Box 212, Folder 6-8, Box 213, Folder 1-3, Box 233)
    - Anarchy in the U.K., circa 1994 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Anderson Valley Advertiser, 1995-1996 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Answer Me, 1993 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Anti Shyster, undated (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Anti-Social Jr., 1984 (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Anti Social Man, 1982 (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - Anvil, 1981 (Box 213, Folder 9)
    - Appearances, 1991-1998 (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - Apple Pie, 1975 (Box 213, Folder 11)
    - Appleton's Journal, 1869 (Box 213, Folder 12)
    - Art Police, 1988-1989 (Box 213, Folder 13)
    - Artless, 1999 (Box 213, Folder 14)
    - Asia, 1923 (Box 213, Folder 15)
    - Aspects, 1964 (Box 213, Folder 16)
    - Ass: Art Star Scene Mag, circa 2003 (Box 213, Folder 17)
    - Atlantic Anarchist Circle, 1998-1999 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Auroville - The City of Human Unity, 1968 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Babushkin's Digest, 2000 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Bad Newz, undated (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Bayou La Rose, 1993 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Beatnik Dreams, 1982 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Beatniks from Space, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Beet, 1995 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Berglers Balz, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Berkeley Barb, 1967 (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Big Hammer, 1990 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Birth and Life Bookstore's Review Newsletter / Catalog: IMPRINTS, 1984 (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - Black Eye, 1988-1990, undated (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - Black Flag, 1986 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Black Mask, 1993 (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - The Black Panther, 1991 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - The Blotter, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 13)
    - Bomb, 1981 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Boneless Boelogna, 1989, undated (Box 214, Folder 14)
    - Boog City, 2002, 2008 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - The Book of Prison Slang, 1993 (Box 214, Folder 15)
    - Boxer, 1997 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - The Boys' Club Record, 1962 (Box 214, Folder 16)
    - A Brave and Beautiful Future ... Could Start Now!, 1982 (Box 214, Folder 17)
    - Breakthrough, 1982 (Box 214, Folder 18)
    - Brick, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 19)
    - Bulletin: Students for a Democratic Society, 1964-1965 (Box 214, Folder 20)
    - Busker's Rag, 1992 (Box 214, Folder 21)
    - Bypass, undated (Box 214, Folder 22)
    - Cabinet, 2004 (Box 214, Folder 23)
    - Campaign to Free Vanunu, 1997 (Box 214, Folder 24)
    - Cancionero Revolucionario, 1947 (Box 214, Folder 25)
    - Capital Times, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 26)
    - Catholic Foam, 1989 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - The Catholic Worker, 1993-2003 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Censorship News, 2000-2001 (Box 215, Folder 3)